Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 10-CB-1541; Amalgamated. Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of N. Am., 1965 (Box 487, Folder 8)
- 10-CB-1542; Local Union of U. A. of Journeymen & Apprentices of Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Ind. Of US & Canada, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 9)
- 10-CB-1555; United Textile Workers, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 10)
- 10-CB-1558; USW, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 11)
- 10-CB-1564; Teamsters Union, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 12)
- 10-CB-1568; Employees of U. of Chicago Bridge & Iron Co., 1965 (Box 487, Folder 13)
- 17-CB-431; Luggage & Novelty Workers U., 1965 (Box 487, Folder 14)
- 17-CB-453; Truck Drivers & Helpers Lo. Union 696, Int. Bro. Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, Helpers of America, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 15)
- 17-CB-455; AFRTA, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 16)
- 1-CB-1007, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 17)
- 1-CB-1009; Sheet Metal Workers, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 18)
- 1-CB-1024; IBT, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 19)
- 1-CB-1063; IBT, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 20)
- 21-CB-1554; I. B. Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of Am. Local 848, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 21)
- The Duty to Bargain in a Non-Compulsory Society, 1960 (Box 487, Folder 22)
- The Wall Street Journal, 1969 (Box 487, Folder 23)
- Region 6 RC Cases, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 24)
- Region 13 CB Cases, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 25)
- Region 13 CC, CD, CP, RM, RD Cases, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 26)
- Region 13 CA Cases, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 27)
- Region 35 RC Cases, 1957-1959 (Box 487, Folder 28)
- Region 6 CB Cases, 1952 (Box 487, Folder 29)
- Mechanization & Modernization, 1960-1966 (Box 487, Folder 30)
- Brooklyn Longshoremen's Medical Center - Report, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 31)
- Final Report of Committee of Inquiry under Rt. Hon. Lord Devlin, 1965 (Box 487, Folder 32)
  Booklet
- Report of Committee of Inquiry into Major Ports of Great Britain, 1962 (Box 487, Folder 33)
- Shipboard Manpower, 1962-1963 (Box 487, Folder 34)
- Men & Machines, 1963 (Box 487, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous (Box 487, Folder 36)
- Ross 620 (Box 487, Folder 37)
  Messenger Envelope
- Monthly Labor Review, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 38)
- Legal & Regulatory Aspects of Coordinated Transportation Service, 1966 (Box 487, Folder 39)
- Emergency Labor Disputes & National Interest, 1950-1963 (Box 487, Folder 40)
- Selected Commodity Unit Costs for Oceanborne Shipments Via Common Carriers (Box 487, Folder 41)
  Binder
- 13-RC-6814; Nu-Way Corporation, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 1)
  Rock Island, IL
- 13-RC-6815; Salerno Megowen Biscuit Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 2)
  Niles, IL
- 13-RC-6817; Prestwor Beverage, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6818 & 13-RC-6819; Frank Beer Distributors, Inc. & Frank Liquor Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6820; National Tea Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 5)
  Freeport, IL
- 13-RC-6821; Weatherhead Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 6)
  Columbia City, IN
- 13-RC-6823; Zeller Packing Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6824; Fairbanks, Morse & Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 8)
  East Moline, IL
- 13-RC-6825; Eisner Grocery Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 9)
  Champaign, IL
- 13-RC-6826; Tharinger Macaroni Co., Division of V. La Rosa & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6827; 20th Century Glove Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6848; Ready Foods Canning Corporation, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 12)
  Cedarburg, WI
- 13-RC-6828; Solo Cup Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6813; Progressive Cafeterias, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6829; Faber Industries, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 15)
  Mason City, IL
- 13-RC-6831; Murphy Construction Company, Murphy Concrete Products Company, Murphy Creek Lime Stone Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 16)
  Black Creek, WI
- 13-RC-6832; Armour & Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 17)
  Rockford, IL
- 13-RC-6833; Harding Williams Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 18)
  Cicero, IL
- 13-RC-6834; Bacon Products, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 19)
  Addison, IL
- 13-RC-6835; Wisconsin Storage Battery Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6836; Chicago Wheel & Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6838; McKesson Liquor Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6839; National Paper Box Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6840; Chicago Bruner Lay Rock Bit Corp., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 24)
  Franklin Park, IL
- 13-RC-6842; Thomas E. Snyder Sons Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6843; General Tinning Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6845; Jos. F. Kiesler Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 27)
  Chicago 22, IL
- 13-RC-6846; Wisco Division of Electric Storage Battery Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6847; Slate Printing Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6849; Austin Gray Iron Foundry Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 30)
  Sheboygan, WI
- 13-RC-6850; Micarta Fabricators, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6852; Lampcraft Industries, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 32)
  Chicago 25, IL
- 13-RC-6855; Mailers Inc. (Addressors Inc.), 1959 (Box 488, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6857; Standard Asbestos Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6858; Estad Products, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 35)
  Westville, IL
- 13-RC-6859; Custom Made Container Co., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6863; Revcor, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 37)
  Carpentersville, IL
- 13-RC-6865; Kroger Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 38)
  Streator, IL
- 13-RC-6867; Bennett Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 39)
  Peotone, IL
- 13-RC-6868; U. S. Plywood Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 40)
  Neenah, WI
- 13-RC-6870; Ensign Coil Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 41)
- 13-RC-6871; Delph-Faber Hide Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 42)
- 13-RC-6872; McKesson Liquor Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 43)
- 13-RC-6873; Stein-Merki Company, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 44)
- 13-RC-6874; Crotty Bros., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 45)
- 13-RC-6876; Filmite Oil Corporation, 1959 (Box 488, Folder 46)
  Butler, WI
- 13-RC-6878; International Printing Ink Corp., Division of Interchemical Corp., 1959 (Box 488, Folder 47)
- The Industrial Revolution in the Eighteenth Century, 1927 (Box 488, Folder 48)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0000, 1964 (Box 489, Folder 1)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0000, 1963 (Box 489, Folder 2)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0000, 1962 (Box 489, Folder 3)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0000, 1961 (Box 489, Folder 4)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0000, 1960 (Box 489, Folder 5)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0001, 1964 (Box 489, Folder 6)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0001, 1963 (Box 489, Folder 7)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0001, 1962 (Box 489, Folder 8)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0001, 1961 (Box 489, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6023; Earl Lithographing & Printing Co., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 1)
  Menasha, WI
- 13-RC-6033; Tuttle & Kif, Inc., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 2)
  Chicago 39, IL
- 13-RC-6076; Chicago Spring Products Company, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6086; H. A. Kuhel Co., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 4)
  Decatur, IL
- 12-RC-654; Daylight Grocery Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 5)
- 12-RC-653; Lindsay Newspapers, Inc., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 6)
  Sarasota, FL
- 12-RC-652; Florida General Linen Supply Company, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 7)
- 12-RC-651; Hot Shoppes, Inc., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 8)
- 12-RC-649; Marie Antoinette Hotel, Prestige Hotels, Inc., 1959 (Box 490, Folder 9)
- 12-RC-657; Jolly Roger Hotel, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 10)
- 12-RC-656; Florida Industrial Laundry Company, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 11)
- 12-RC-655; Lakeland Cement Company, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 12)
- 12-RC-695; Flint Ink Corporation, 1959 (Box 490, Folder 13)
- 1-CA-2702; Peerless Motor Express Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 1)
  Hartford, CT
- 1-CA-2674; Sumner Williams Company, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 2)
  East Boston, MA
- 1-CA-2678; Enterprise Department Stores, Inc. d/b/a J. M. Fields Discount Stores, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 3)
  Medford, MA
- 1-CA-2684; Metals & Controls Corporation, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 4)
  Attleboro, MA
- 1-CA-2683; Metals & Controls Corporation, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 5)
- 1-CA-2691; Royal McBee Corporation, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 6)
- 1-CA-2692; Roadway Express, Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 7)
  West Haven, CT
- 1-CA-2697; Roadway Express, Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 8)
- 1-CA-2694; Roadway Express, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 9)
- 1-CA-2696; Howe Scale Company, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 10)
  Rutland, VT
- Union Financial Statistics, 1959-1960 (Box 491, Folder 11)
- MLP - List of Camps - NYS Health Dept. (Box 491, Folder 12)
- 1-CA-2703; Wilbar's, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 13)
  Boston, MA & N. Haven, CT
- 1-CA-2698; Jordan Marsh Company, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 14)
  Peabody, MA
- 1-CA-2699; Bradley-Smith Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 15)
- 1-CA-2701; Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 16)
  Boston, CA
- 1-CA-2620; Trawler Brighton, Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 17)
- 1-CA-2441; Albany Novelty Corp., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 18)
  North Bennington, VT
- 1-CA-2681; Enterprise Department Stores, Inc. d/b/a J. M. Fields Discount Stores, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-4230; American-Marietta Company, 1960 (Box 491, Folder 20)
- 1-CA-2744; Daniel P. Quinn, Contractor, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 21)
  Thompsonville, CT
- 1-CA-2615; Lehman Bros., Inc., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 22)
- 1-CA-2625; Carpenter Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 491, Folder 23)
  Somerville, MA
- 1-CA-2704; The Connecticut Water Company, 1959 (Box 491, Folder 24)
  Clinton, CT
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1964 (Box 492, Folder 1)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1963 (Box 492, Folder 2)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1962 (Box 492, Folder 3)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1961 (Box 492, Folder 4)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1960 (Box 492, Folder 5)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1964 (Box 492, Folder 6)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1963 (Box 492, Folder 7)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1962 (Box 492, Folder 8)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1961 (Box 492, Folder 9)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1960 (Box 492, Folder 10)
- 1-CA-2069; Hannaford Bros. Co. (T. R. Savage Division) [Folder 1 of 4], 1956-1959 (Box 493, Folder 1)
  Bangor, ME
- 1-CA-2069; Hannaford Bros. Co. (T. R. Savage Division) [Folder 2 of 4], 1956-1959 (Box 493, Folder 2)
- 1-CA-2069; Hannaford Bros. Co. (T. R. Savage Division) [Folder 3 of 4], 1956-1959 (Box 493, Folder 3)
- 1-CA-2069; Hannaford Bros. Co. (T. R. Savage Division) [Folder 4 of 4], 1956-1959 (Box 493, Folder 4)
- 1-CA-1853; Boston Record-American-Advertiser Division Hearst Corp. [Folder 1 of 3], 1955-1959 (Box 493, Folder 5)
- 1-CA-1853; Boston Record-American-Advertiser Division Hearst Corp. [Folder 2 of 3], 1955-1959 (Box 493, Folder 6)
- 1-CA-1853; Boston Record-American-Advertiser Division Hearst Corp. [Folder 3 of 3], 1955-1959 (Box 493, Folder 7)
- 1-CA-1860; Boston Record-American-Advertiser Division Hearst Corp., 1955 (Box 493, Folder 8)
- 1-CA-2927; Lagasse Furniture Company, Brentwood Lounge Company, 1959 (Box 493, Folder 9)
  Haverhill, MA
- 1-CA-1916; New England Die Casting Co. [Folder 1 of 3], 1955-1958 (Box 493, Folder 10)
- 1-CA-1916; New England Die Casting Co. [Folder 2 of 3], 1955-1958 (Box 493, Folder 11)
- 1-CA-1916; New England Die Casting Co. [Folder 3 of 3], 1955-1958 (Box 493, Folder 12)
- 1-CA-2267; New England Upholstery Co. [Folder 1 of 2], 1957-1960 (Box 493, Folder 13)
  Methuen, MA
- 1-CA-2267; New England Upholstery Co. [Folder 2 of 2], 1957-1959 (Box 493, Folder 14)
- 1-CA-2908; Packing Machinery Company, 1959 (Box 493, Folder 15)
  East Longmeadow, MA
- 1-CA-2871; Fred P. Wolfe Jr. d/b/a Wolfe's Quality Food Shop, 1959 (Box 493, Folder 16)
- 1-CA-2872; Fred P. Wolfe Jr. d/b/a Wolfe's Quality Foods, 1959 (Box 493, Folder 17)
- 1-CA-2873; Fred P. Wolfe d/b/a Wolfe's Quality Food Shop, 1959 (Box 493, Folder 18)